dresses.com 2005-12-10

# Dresses.com - Privacy and Security Statement

****DRESSES.COM PRIVACY POLICY****  

This Privacy Policy is effective for all users of the DRESSES.COM website (hereinafter, "User"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide you with ODETTE CHRISTIANE, LLC (hereinafter "DRESSES.COM," "we," "us" or "our") information collection practices (including the information DRESSES.COM collects, how it is collected, and the circumstances under which the information is disclosed), and to demonstrate DRESSES.COM�s firm commitment to privacy and adherence to the California Online Privacy Protection Act. 

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website DRESSES.COM:

**SECURE SITE**

Our site uses an online secure order form for customers to apply. When your order is placed through our secure online server, or you send us an email, we collect confidential customer information. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all order information you input before it is sent to us. We designed Dresses.com to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; for example, 3.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator and versions 3.02 or higher of Internet Explorer. This means you'll be unable to inadvertently place an order through an unsecured connection. When you send us an email (as distinguished from a secure order form, which is encrypted), it is not necessarily secure and is not encrypted. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. It is our policy to never send private information, such as your credit card number, via e-mail.

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

The customer information that is collected to process your order might include contact information (name, mailing address, telephone number, fax number and/or email address) and financial information (checking account, name on account, credit card number and expiration date), depending upon the nature of your order.

The contact information is used to process your request. The customer's contact and financial information is private and confidential. All information is secured and maintained on-file in our corporate office in Canoga Park, California and is sometimes used to contact the customer for purposes of completing the order requested by the customer. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer and this information is not shared with anyone outside of our company, except the merchant bank for the processing of credit card orders.

**REVIEW & CHANGES TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

Our hosting service logs IP addresses, browser types and referred logs, which are used by our marketing staff for internal purposes only. Users can call DRESSES.COM to remove contact and/or financial information from our databases and to not receive any future communications from us or to change or modify any contact and/or financial information previously provided to us.

**PROMOTIONS**

To preserve customer's anonymity and to assure the quality of customer communications, DRESSES.COM provides customers with the opportunity to "opt-in" to any further marketing promotions. Information that you provide to us when you order, enter our contest, or request a catalog are maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. Furthermore, DRESSES.COM will never release this information to other parties. 

**DISCLOSURE TO OUTSIDE PARTIES**

Aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information may be provided to reputable third parties, but these statistics contain no personally identifying information. However, DRESSES.COM may release client account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, prevent fraud, enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or to otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of DRESSES.COM, our customers or other third parties.

**SECURITY STATEMENT**  

Dresses.com believes in providing a safe and secure shopping experience for all of our customers. We provide only the most stingent of security measures available on the Internet. We want you to feel comfortable that personal information such as your credit card number will be kept safe throughout your entire shopping experience at Dresses.com. 

It is our policy to never send private information, such as your credit card number, via e-mail. In fact, this is a policy we recommend you adopt in all of your Internet activities. 

We designed Dresses.com to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; for example, 3.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator and versions 3.02 or higher of Internet Explorer. This means you'll be unable to inadvertently place an order through an unsecured connection. 

**COOKIES**

DRESSES.COM may use outside companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies (pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes while at the site). While we use cookies in other parts of our site, our ad company collects cookies received with banner ads and we do not have any access to this information.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by DRESSES.COM. 

**CHANGES TO SITE**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**EFFECTIVE DATE**

This Privacy Policy is effective this 1st day of August, 2004.
